# **Delmy Melendez**

delmymm93@gmail.com | 435-513-1099 | Heber City, UT

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/delmy-melendez-8961721b4/ | Github: https://github.com/delmymm

# **Profile**

I have 7 years in customer service management, with leading a department of my own. Able to train others and learn from others as well. Highly professional with extensive training in computer programs, and customer service techniques. Comfortable in a fast paced environment, exceptionally fast learner. Currently enrolled in a full stack program.

### Skills

- Known programming languages: HTML, CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap and some Node JS.
- Great organization skills
- Adapt to diverse groups
- Problem solving skills
- Professional demeanor
- Interpersonal skills
- High energy
- Social perceptiveness
- Bilingual (English and Spanish)

#### Education

High School Diploma

Wasatch High School Heber City, UT 2011

University of Utah Full Stack Web Development program - current

## References

Stephany Perez , 435.513.1753

Kiara Lopez, 801.455.3058

Coral Gramse, 385.424.2328

# **Professional Experience**

October 2019 - Present Chartsquad, Communications Lead

- Possess knowledge of HIPAA and HITECH federal laws
- Data entry
- Determined how to effectively handle situations when problems arose
- Fulfill each client's needs to the best of my ability
- Thoroughly review and process patients PHI

October 2016 - Present One Stop House Cleaning, Administrative Assistant

- Track employee hours worked on Excel
- Worked collaboratively in a team environment
- Developed positive customer relationships through friendly meetings and customer service
- Prioritized and accomplished wide range of tasks each shift
- Resolved all customer complaints in a professional manner while prioritizing the customer

November 2013 - October 2017 All Resort Group, Guest Services Manager

- Wrote company memos on various policies
- Answered customer calls promptly in an appropriate manner
- Asked open ended questions to assess customers needs
- Processed cash and credit card payments rapidly and accurately
- Investigated and resolved customer inquiries and complaints in a timely and empathic manner